NICOLE VOWELL

Professional | GAME | VR | NFT & Web3 developer



EXPERIENCE

Team Leader

Crimessi Inc.

- · Established a creative team, focus on the paticipation from my team
- set up a strategy with our customers and focus on a customer-first policy.
- Oriented toward a wonderful game deploy that helps with education and children's growth.
- Boosted team productivity by 15%, resulting in reduced project delivery times for VR game development.
- Oversaw the implementation of robust cybersecurity measures, significantly reducing vulnerability to cyber threats.
- Provided technical support to colleagues, resolving issues related to hardware, software, and network connectivity promptly.

Game Developer

Metalife

d 07/2018 - 07/2021

Hong Kong

- · Trained and supervised team to deliver on customer targets
- Increased user retention by 25% through enhanced in-game features and
- Enhanced multiplayer engagement by 50% by introducing innovative features and dynamic challenges.
- Worked on a portfolio containing 25 games, each with a unique design incorporating cutting-edge VR elements.
- Launched a cross-platform title that saw a 200% increase in daily active users by enhancing multiplayer features.
- Increased NFT transaction value by 40% by integrating blockchain features into virtual environments.
- Enhanced VR game performance, leading to a 30% reduction in load

Metaverse/Web3 & NFT Engineer

MWT

★ 07/2022 - Present

Hong Kong

Developed car racing PC game (Web3) inspired by Forza on Arbitrum blockchain

Skilled Unreal Engine 4,5 Developer

UME

- · Developed a web3 shooter game on Solana Blockchain using lyra framework
- Skilled in using C++ for performance-critical aspects of game development, including custom gameplay mechanics and engine
- Rigging and animating characters and objects, integrating animation into Unreal Engine, and using the Animation Blueprint for complex animation states.
- Implementing LOD techniques to optimize game performance without compromising visual quality.

EDUCATION

Master's in Computer Science & Software Engineering

City University of Hong Kong (CityU) **ii** 02/2014 - 02/2018

SUMMARY

I'm an experienced Game Developer with a strong focus on Unreal Engine A, VR development in Unity , and pioneering Web 3.0/NFT technologies (11).

As for my personal characteristics, I thrive on challenges and I work well under pressure.

Particularly, I am excited about Metaverse game and it requires all my skills.

KEY ACHIEVEMENTS



My advantage

I would describe myself as detail-oriented and I am an eager leaner.

SKILLS

Blueprint

C++

Blender

Unity

Lyra

AR/VR Development

Mobile Game Development

PC Game Development

Web GL

Three.js

Smart Contracts

Maya

3D Modeling

3D Modeling

3D Animation

Surface painter

Z-Brush

Environment and Level Design

Online multiplayer

network replication

Cinematics

Streaming

Simulations

Al development

procedural generation

Strategy Games

Racing Games

LANGUAGES

English

Advanced •

Native •

Chinese Russian

Advanced • • •

Powered by Enhancy